virtuosimedia.com 2012-06-13

# Privacy Policy

#### Definitions

| 

The Personal Information Protection Act ('PIPA') governs the collection, use and disclosure of personal information by organizations in a manner that recognizes both the right of individuals to protect their personal information and the need of organizations to collect, use or disclose personal information for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in the circumstances.

This Privacy Policy ('Policy') describes Virtuosi Media's (VM) use and sharing of personally identifiable information ('PII') that users voluntarily provide to VM when they register. PII include your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, or credit card number. The Term 'User' refers to a visitor, a registered user, or client. This Privacy Policy applies to the Services offered by VM, including any VM Website or Software.  
  
#### Modification

| 

We reserve the right, at any time, to change or modify the terms and conditions applicable to your subscription. Such changes can be accessed at any time using the "Privacy Policy" link at the bottom of each page. Your continued use of our service(s) after such a change(s) has been made indicates your acceptance of any such changes. It is important that you review this Agreement periodically to be aware of any such revisions. We may alter, suspend or discontinue any Service or part thereof at any time, including the availability of any Service feature, database or content without notice or liability.  
  
#### Collection and Use of Personal Information

| 

We maintain the confidentiality of all our User's information. VM will not use or disclose your personal information for purposes other than those described in this policy.

We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit or use our pages. We may also receive PII from our business partners. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. VM does not gather any specific personal information from you, such as your name, phone number or e-mail address unless you supply it by sending us an email or by filling out a form in a secure portion of the site.  
  
#### Cookies

| 

Cookies are small bits of information that VM places on your computer. VM may use cookies to identify your Internet browser, store Users' preferences, and determine whether you have installed the software needed to access certain Services. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide services.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Virtuosi Media may use Google AdSense to deliver ads to our website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads).  
  
#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

| 

We reserve the right to send electronic mail to you, for the purpose of informing you of changes or additions to the Service, or of any VM related products and services. We reserve the right to disclose information about your usage of the Service and demographics in forms that do not reveal your personal identity.

Except as described in this Policy, VM will not share your PII with third parties (excluding those set out in this Policy) unless you have given VM permission to do so.

We may use this information for the following general purposes:

  1. to customize the content you see,
  2. to inform you of special offers or notices that may be of interest to you;
  3. to send the information to companies who work on behalf of VM to provide Services (including but not limited to instant messaging and advertising) to you. These companies do not have any right to use the personal information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us;
  4. to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
  5. to refer you to authorities if we find that your actions on our website are illegal.

#### Resale of Information to Third Parties

| 

Personally Identifiable Information is not sold to third parties, under any circumstances.  
  
#### External Links

| 

This web site may contain links to other sites. VM is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of each site you visit before using them. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this website. VM does not research or endorse any product or service appearing in ads on this site or any websites reached as a result of clicking an external link.  
  
#### Children's Personal Information

| 

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ('COPPA') applies to the online collection of personal information from children under 13. VM and this Site are not intended for children under the age of 13 years and as such we will not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. Parents and legal guardians are encouraged to monitor their children's Internet usage and to instruct their children to never provide personal information on this Site or any other site without their permission.  
  
#### Copyright Infringement

| 

If you believe that any material or content distributed by VM constitutes copyright infringement, please provide us with the following information: an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest; a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed; a description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on our website; your address, telephone number and email address; a written statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner's behalf.  
  
#### Indemnity

| 

VM shall not be liable for any damages or injury resulting from your access to, or using this site, or any information provided at this site. Everything on the site is provided to you "as is" without warrantee of any kind. VM does not warrant that the functions contained in the materials will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, that the information is up-to-date or complete, or that this site or the server that makes it available are free of viruses or other harmful components. You hereby agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless VM and all officers, directors, owners, information providers, affiliates, licensors and licensees from and against any and all liability and costs, including, without limitation, reasonable attorneys' fees, incurred by the indemnified parties in connection with any claim or loss caused by your use or reliance on information obtained through the content distributed by VM arising out of the use or inability to use VM Services or caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, communication line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to and/or alteration of the VM Site.  
  
#### Miscellaneous

| 

All claims, or disputes which may arise out of the performance, or in any way relating to this Site and any and all other VM Sites shall be governed by the laws of the Province of British Columbia, Canada. VM also have no responsibility, and shall not be liable for viruses that may infect your computer equipment or other property on account of your access to, use of, or browsing in the Site or your downloading of any data, text, images, video, or any materials from the Site. Headings are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect.
